Anton Bogomazov

Backend Software Engineer

Software Engineer with 3 years' experience specializing in Java and Kotlin in the context of web development. Focusing on project benefits rather than personal preferences, emphasizing practices over tools, and striving to collaborate and share knowledge.

+381 64 3506945 Belgrade, Serbia

abogomazov.com abogomazov.dev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/abogomazov

EXPERIENCE

Kotlin Software Engineer, Holland and Barrett

January 2024 - Present

British-based multinational chain of health food shops with over 1,300 stores in 16 countries.

Software Engineer, Setronica

August 2022 - January 2024

International software development company with extensive expertise, including eCommerce, online marketplaces, ERP, and eProcurement.

- Maintained a mature system with multiple programming languages for both backend and frontend (java, js/ts, python) in a cloud-based business network and supply chain payments platform.
- Provided engineering support for data science projects.
- Led mentorship project for Java engineers.

Lead Kotlin Software Engineer, Beeline (VimpelCom)

April 2022 - August 2022

One of the largest telecom companies in the CIS region, with a revenue of 4.65 billion USD in 2018 and a team of 28,500 employees.

- Led and trained a team of 6 engineers in the development of an application for aggregating users and services data.
- Refined the service's inherently flawed architecture.
- Introduced CI/CD, development and testing practices.
- Delivered and deployed the first releases.
- Migrated over 30,000 data records from legacy systems and resolved conflicts.

Kotlin/Java Software Engineer, Domclick

December 2020 - April 2022

A real estate service enables users to buy, sell and rent properties with an annual turnover exceeding 135 million USD, attracting 15.6 million monthly visits.

- Designed pledge property and mortgage services, increasing product revenues by 6%.
- Improved DX by automating everyday engineering tasks such as artifact delivery, saving developers 1 hour/day.
- Tuned service performance to increase the availability up to 99.95%.
- Resolved over 20 customer escalations and 4 critical production incidents.

Content Manager, Ultimate Guitar

August 2017 - December 2020

One of the world's largest websites for musicians, attracting over 50 million monthly visits.

 Created over 1,000 top-notch scores and arrangements for the Official Tabs project.

SKILLS

Engineering

Object-Oriented and Functional Design Principles Domain-Driven Design Extreme Programming **Programming Languages** Java, Kotlin, Python, JS, C **Frameworks** Spring, Ktor

DatabasesPostgres, Hibernate, jOOQ,
Exposed, Liquibase

Testing

Junit, Kotest, ArchUnit, Rest-assured, Selenium

Rest-assured, Selenium

Messaging
RabbitMQ, Kafka

DevOps Tools

Docker, Kubernetes

Monitoring and Logging

ELK, Grafana, Prometheus,
7abbix

EDUCATION

Ecole 42 Moscow Campus

Computer Science
December 2019 - January 2021
École 42 is a private institution
of higher education in CS,
based on peer-to-peer and
project-based learning.

RZGMU Medical University General practitioner September 2014 - August 2019 Studied natural and medical sciences.

LANGUAGES

English, Full working proficiency

Russian, Native